gdgt.com 2011-12-03

# Privacy policy - gdgt

gdgt's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using gdgt, located at gdgt.com ("gdgt" or "Website").

By using or accessing gdgt, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions regarding this statement, please use our [contact form](http://gdgt.com/contact/) to send us an email. 

### The Information We Collect

When you visit gdgt you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register with gdgt, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your zip code, your birth date, your gender and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter gdgt, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all gdgt visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies for several purposes, including to confirm that users are logged in. By default, these cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. In the event that a user clicks "remember me" at time of login, we use a persistent cookie that stores information to make it easier for you to login when you come back to gdgt. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

When you use gdgt, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time.

You post Your Content (as defined in the gdgt [Terms of Service](http://gdgt.com/tos/)) on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that Your Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Your Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your Your Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on gdgt is a violation of the gdgt Terms of Service and should be reported by using our [contact form](http://gdgt.com/contact/) to send us an email.

By using gdgt, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States. 

### Children Under Age 13

gdgt does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for gdgt or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on gdgt. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us through our [contact form](http://gdgt.com/contact/). 

### Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18

We recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. 

### Use of Information Obtained by gdgt

When you register with gdgt, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people as specified in your privacy settings to enable you to connect with people on gdgt. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by gdgt that we think you may find valuable.

Profile information is used by gdgt primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings.

Profile information you submit to gdgt will be available to users of gdgt as indicated by your privacy settings (e.g., everyone, friends-only, no one). Your name, network names, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across the gdgt network and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends can find you and send a friend request. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship to you (friend or if you are a follower of said person, etc.) that allows such access based on your privacy settings.

gdgt may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.

Generally, you may opt out of such emails from the Settings page on your Profile account, though gdgt reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

gdgt may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like a specific product or personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you gdgt. We believe this benefits you. You can know more about the world around you and, where there are advertisements, they're more likely to be interesting to you. For example, if you put own an iPhone, we might serve you an advertisement highlighting iPhone cases. But we don't tell the case manufacture who you are. 

### Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

  * gdgt is about sharing information with others -- friends and people in your networks -- while providing you with privacy settings that restrict other users from accessing your information. We allow you to choose the information you provide to friends and networks through gdgt. Our network architecture and your privacy settings allow you to make informed choices about who has access to your information. We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. 
  * We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about gdgt, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the gdgt-specified purposes. 
  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the gdgt service or using the gdgt name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. 
  * We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through on-site offers. 
  * If the ownership of all or substantially all of the gdgt business, or individual business units owned by gdgt were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

When you use gdgt, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos, Marketplace listings or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, Marketplace listings or other items, this information may become publicly available. 

### Links

gdgt may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by gdgt. 

### Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on gdgt are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. gdgt does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on gdgt unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by gdgt and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers. 

### Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on gdgt is readily available through the profile editing tools. gdgt users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their gdgt account may do so using our [contact form](http://gdgt.com/contact/) to send us an email. Removed information may persist indefinitely but will not be generally available to the public or to members of gdgt.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on gdgt, however, (e.g., sending a message to another gdgt user) you generally cannot remove such communications. 

### Security 

gdgt takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). (To learn more about SSL, go to <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer>). Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. 

### Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of gdgt, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
